<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="privacy_title">Privacy</string>
    <string name="privacy_personal_auth">My Information &amp; Authorizations</string>
    <string name="privacy_data_collection">Personal Information</string>
    <string name="privacy_data_collection_list">Personal Information Collected</string>
    <string name="privacy_third_share">Information Shared with Third Parties</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_summary">Privacy Policy Summary</string>
    <string name="privacy_agreement">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_user_agreement">Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="privacy_system_auth">System Permissions</string>
    <string name="privacy_personal_info">My Information</string>
    <string name="privacy_camera">Camera</string>
    <string name="privacy_microphone">Microphone</string>
    <string name="privacy_avatar">Profile Photo</string>
    <string name="privacy_beauty">Beauty</string>
    <string name="privacy_allow">Allow</string>
    <string name="privacy_deny">Deny</string>
    <string name="privacy_name">Name</string>
    <string name="privacy_id">ID</string>
    <string name="privacy_phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="privacy_email">Email</string>
    <string name="privacy_system_setting">Go to System Settings</string>
    <string name="privacy_none">None</string>
    <string name="privacy_tip_copy">Copied</string>
    <string name="privacy_manage">Manage %1$s access</string>
    <string name="privacy_desc">You can check %1$s\'s collection of your personal information.</string>
    <string name="privacy_beauty_face_request">When you use the tencent effect beautification function, we will perform real-time intelligent recognition of the facial pixel information captured by your camera or pictures you selected from media store. During this process, we will collect your facial pixel information in real-time to provide you with better beautification effects. We will not store or associate your facial pixel information in any form. This information is sensitive personal information, so please provide it with caution. If you do not authorize it, you will not be able to use this function. After authorization, you can disable this function in privacy settings at any time.</string>
    <string name="privacy_app_name">Tencent Cloud Media Services</string>
    <string name="privacy_camera_des">%1$s Needs access to your camera, and it can be used for functions such as Interactive Video Streaming, Show Live, Live Push, Video Call, Group Video Call, Multi-person audio, video room and Avatar speech etc.</string>
    <string name="privacy_mic_des">%1$s Needs access to your microphone, and it can be used for functions such as Interactive Video Streaming, Show Live, Video Call, Live Push, Group Video Call, Multi-person audio, video room, short video production, conversational chat and Avatar, etc.</string>
    <string name="privacy_storage">Storage</string>
    <string name="privacy_storage_des">%1$s need to access your storage permission, which can be used for local video editing, chorus, three-screen co-shooting, saving videos and screenshots after being enabled.</string>
    <string name="privacy_avatar_title">Avatar</string>
    <string name="privacy_beauty_face_not_auth">Beauty feature is not authorized. To enable Beauty, please go to [Profile] - [Privacy] - [My Information &amp; Authorizations] and turn on Beauty authorization.</string>
    <string name="privacy_tencent_effect_avatar_face_request">When using Avatar-related features, we will perform real-time intelligent recognition of the facial pixel information captured from you. During this process, we will collect your facial pixel information in real-time to provide you with better virtual avatar generation effects. We will not store or associate your facial pixel information in any form. This information is sensitive personal information, please provide it with caution. If you do not authorize it, you will not be able to use this feature. You can also disable this feature in privacy settings at any time.</string>
    <string name="privacy_purpose">Purpose of usage</string>
    <string name="privacy_use_by_register_login">For registration and login</string>
    <string name="privacy_use_by_register_use">For registration and using %1$s features</string>
    <string name="privacy_alert_welcome_title">Welcome to %1$s</string>
    <string name="privacy_alert_disagree">Disagree</string>
    <string name="privacy_alert_agree_continue">Agree &amp; Continue</string>
    <string name="privacy_alert_full_content">%1$s is a product provided by Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd. (35th Floor, Tencent Building, Kejizhong 1st Road, Maling Community, Yuehai Street, Nanshan District, Shenzhen). It offers features including interactive live streaming, co-anchoring, karaoke, audio/video chat, and online conferencing. For a quick look at how we collect personal information, see the %2$s.\n\n1. When you sign up with or log in to RT-Cube, we collect your profile information including name, photo, mobile number, and email address. When an error occurs during your use of our services, we collect your package name, system version, and process name, among others. We collect only information essential for you to use our product and services. To learn more about the personal information we collect and how we use it, see %3$s.\n\n2. When you use features such as interactive live streaming, co-anchoring, karaoke, audio/video chat, and online conferencing, we may access your storage space, camera, photos, mic, and network, among others. We will ask for your permission the first time we access these resources. You can deny access or change the access settings.\n\n3. Some of our services are provided by third parties. To learn about the third parties we work with and how we share information with them, see %4$s.\n\n4. You can query, copy, update, or delete your personal information, as well as withdraw your consent for data collection. You can also delete your account. To learn more about your rights over your personal information, see Part 5 of the %5$s.\n\n5. If you have any questions, contact us at Dataprivacy@tencent.com or via other channels provided in the %5$s.\n\n</string>
    <string name="privacy_alert_content_agree">If you agree to the %1$s, %2$s, %3$s, and %4$s, click Agree to start using our product and services.</string>
    <string name="privacy_report_title">Report</string>
    <string name="privacy_report_type_title">Report Type</string>
    <string name="privacy_report_type_politics">Sensitive</string>
    <string name="privacy_report_type_porn">Pornography</string>
    <string name="privacy_report_type_personal_attacks">Abuse</string>
    <string name="privacy_report_type_violence">Bloody</string>
    <string name="privacy_report_type_ad">Advertise</string>
    <string name="privacy_report_type_scam">Scam</string>
    <string name="privacy_report_type_illegal">Illegal</string>
    <string name="privacy_report_type_other">Other</string>
    <string name="privacy_report_description">Report Description</string>
    <string name="privacy_report_description_placeholder">Please describe your report</string>
    <string name="privacy_report_submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="privacy_report_submit_success">Submitted successfully</string>
</resources>
